Ukwuoma Tochukwu

Owerri Municipal, Imo, Nigeria



ukwuomatochi112@gmail.com



08169039269



linkedin.com/in/ukwuoma-tochukwu

Summary

I'm a software developer with 1+ years' of experience specializing in frontend web development.

I design and build highly responsive web pages and applications.

I'm a creative person and that plays a good role in my work.

So far, I have HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, React, MySql, PHP, and Git/GitHub in my skill set.

I'm still enthusiastically learning other frameworks and programming languages on the go.

I have led a team of developers during my internships with different companies in delivering tasks efficiently.

I'm always open to learning and improving my skills.

Experience

Side Hustle React Developer

Side Hustle

Apr 2022 - Jul 2022 (4 months)

As a react developer intern at Side hustle, I learned and applied ReactJS in building responsive web pages and applications.

I led a team of five interns in carrying out tasks effectively and delivering within the time given.

It was a nice experience.



Full-stack Developer

Anhydraze

Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 (6 months)

During this period of training, I learned the basics of frontend and backend development using ReactJS and Laravel in the respective tracks.

I contributed to building the company's official website as a backend developer.

Student Intern

Oluaka Institute of Technology

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022 (5 months)

I learned the basics of frontend web development and how to use the version control system, GitHub.

Education



👖 Nnamdi Azikiwe University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Mathematics

Licenses & Certifications

- SH-IT-0033635
- Soft skill training Jobberman Youth Engagement & Learning

Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Laravel • JavaScript • PHP • MySQL • Git • React.js • HTML5 • Communication